outwar.com 2005-12-16

# Outwar.com - Massive online role-playing game (RPG)!

**Privacy Statement  
**outwar.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: outwar.com

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address for statistical purposes. It allows outwar.com to determine how many users are visiting the site during the course of the day. This is the only use of the IP.

**Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to determine the last time a visitor has logged in and the last time an advertisement was viewed.

**Advertisers**  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here <<http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>>

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Personal Information**  
We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. outwar.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. E-mail addresses of outwar.com subscribers remain protected by our custom software.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [privacy@outwar.com](mailto:privacy@outwar.com)
